Ace this is Fvckin Flames
من بعد الhood
Full تشباتي mayne
They tryna reach me illuminati بس
Diamonds dancing on my wrist
تقول سمره نقازي
VVS on my Casio
ترا شي مو عادي
سبحان الله تكلم عني
He end up بالرازي
قاعد اسوي الي ببالي
انا paste وانتو copy
راد بقوة kamikaze
اذبحهم Kingpin الي قالي
So don’t waste my time
اطلع من حياتي
Shoutout to Scooter finesse ma hoppy
From Kuwait to Atlanta
Salam Ma Akhees
Tryna stick to صلاتي
Fresh to death
لي مماتي
الحمدلله
Living good
im goin up
Level up
Getting فلوس
Everyday
تقول مجبوس
Haters
ما اشوف
جيب عليه motivation
ماكو breaks بس ادوس
الحمدلله
Living good
im goin up
Level up
Getting فلوس
Everyday
تقول مجبوس
Haters
ما اشوف
جيب عليه motivation
ماكو breaks بس اد وس
Imma keep 100
قعدت مع Kingpin
قالي
Pull some strings
خنشوف
The whole team win
يارب ان شاء الله
I don’t sin
وضعي حجي Elchapo
Status 7aji Kingpin
انت خلك عالثلج
Diamonds on me bling bling
I get the bag no migos
Paid in full like rico
من فوق لي تحت Supzero
اهني
Gang Gang Gang Gang
3al Neck baby Ice age
ما يدور شي تقليد
sky dweller big face
Enshallah I don’t lose my Faith
قاعد
Shotgun bel Wraith
Abe 6 digits no fame
انت خال بس lame
صعب حجي تصيد غلطه
الhype  تقول قلطه
لي الحيني
Too much sauce
They still askin
عالخلطه
الحمدلله
Living good
im goin up
Level up
Getting فلوس
Everyday
تقول مجبوس
Haters
ما اشوف
جيب عليه motivation
ماكو breaks بس ادوس
الحمدلله
Living good
im goin up
Level up
Getting فلوس
Everyday
تقول مجبوس
Haters
ما اشوف
جيب عليه motivation
ماكو breaks بس ادوس
Abdullah Trill #الحمدالله